{
    "availableCourses": [
        {
            "id": "React Js",
            "course": "React Js",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "id": "q1",
                    "question": "React js was invented as a contribution to web dev by ___ team",                    "choices": {
                        "A": "Microsoft",
                        "B": "Facebook",
                        "C": "Google",
                        "D": "Google DEV"
                    },
                    "answer": "Facebook"
                },
                {
                    "id": "q2",
                    "question": "React js is based on ____ component use",
                    "choices": {
                        "A": "Functional",
                        "B": "Componental",
                        "C": "Obect Javascript",
                        "D": "Declerative"
                    },
                    "answer": "Functional"
                },{
                    "id": "q3",
                    "question": "We use useState hooke in react js for ?",
                    "choices": {
                        "A": "State Management",
                        "B": "Code life cycle",
                        "C": "State Deprecation",
                        "D": "State Formation"
                    },
                    "answer": "State Management"
                },{
                    "id": "q4",
                    "question": "React js use useEffect Hooke for ___ ?",
                    "choices": {
                        "A": "Code Life cycle",
                        "B": "Function call",
                        "C": "State Deprecation",
                        "D": "Context"
                    },
                    "answer": "Code Life cycle"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": "JavaScript",
            "course": "JavaScript",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "id": "q1",
                    "question": "JS Stands for ____ ?",
                    "choices": {
                        "A": "JavaScript",
                        "B": "Java Scripting",
                        "C": "Jam Sculpturing",
                        "D": "I dont Know"
                    },
                    "answer": "JavaScript"
                },
                {
                    "id": "q2",
                    "question": "JavaScript was originally called Livescript, why?",
                    "choices": {
                        "A": "It is uesd to add styling properties to document",
                        "B": "It is used to style links and hrefs",
                        "C": "It is used to add functionality to documents",
                        "D": "It is Declerative"
                    },
                    "answer": "It is used to add functionality to documents"
                },{
                    "id": "q3",
                    "question": "Javascript became standardized as ___",
                    "choices": {
                        "A": "Ecmascript",
                        "B": "CodeScript",
                        "C": "LiveScript",
                        "D": "DocumentScript"
                    },
                    "answer": "State Management"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "id": "Html",
            "course": "Html",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "id": "q1",
                    "question": "HTML Stands for ____ ?",
                    "choices": {
                        "A": "HyperTextMarkUpLanguage",
                        "B": "HyperTestMarkingLanguage",
                        "C": "HyperTextMockUpLanguage",
                        "D": "HappyDocumentTexting"
                    },
                    "answer": "HyperTextMarkUpLanguage"
                },
                {
                    "id": "q2",
                    "question": "HTML is used for document text ____",
                    "choices": {
                        "A": "Formatting",
                        "B": "Typing",
                        "C": "Lamination",
                        "D": "Bioler Plate"
                    },
                    "answer": "Formatting"
                },{
                    "id": "q3",
                    "question": "Divs are used for ___",
                    "choices": {
                        "A": "Creating Inline containers",
                        "B": "Creating Block container",
                        "C": "Spanning Buttons",
                        "D": "Word container"
                    },
                    "answer": "Creating Block container"
                }
            ]
        }
    ],
    "registeredUser": [
      {
        "email": "adekunlkemartins@gmail.com",
        "password": "Adekunle111"
      },
      {
        "email": "elliotliucky509@gmail.com",
        "password": "Elliot123"
      }
    ]
}